<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.icapps.niddler</id>
    <name>Niddler</name>
    <version>2.8.2</version>
    <vendor email="support@chimerapps.com" url="https://www.icapps.com">Chimerapps &amp; icapps</vendor>

    <description>This plugin enables the niddler ui inside the IDE</description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <p>
        <b>2.8.2</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Searching and syntax hightlighting is now supported in pretty/raw view!</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.8.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed issue where dart stacktraces would not highlight</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.8.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Added extra configuration option to automatically start niddler when running your code. This is saved per project</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.7.2</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Desaturate icon in session tab header when connection is lost</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.7.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Show server icon in session tab header if supplied</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.7.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Observe the console for niddler server messages and allow direct connections</li>
            <li><p>Support for icons in the session discovery. Out of the box supported: android,apple,dart,flutter.</p>
            <p>If you want to support custom icons or overwrite the defaults, place bitmaps (png,bmp,...) in the .idea/niddler folder (square 20x20 or 40x40 with @2x), matching happens by file name (without extension).</p>
            <p>Update the server code with the requested icon using the provided libraries for dart/java/android</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.6.6</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Add array position indicator to json structured rendering</li>
            <li>When no content-type headers are sent, try to check if we are an image by using some magic numbers</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.6.5</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed exported rewrite rule not being imported by charles</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.6.4</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Enhanced icons to account for people with color-blindness</li>
            <li>Fixed network headers not always showing up in detail panel</li>
            <li>Curl export will now export network request when possible, containing cookies, ...</li>
            <li>Curl export will add a flag to decompress the output when appropriate</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.6.3</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed debugger not connecting if rewrite rules are not enabled</li>
            <li>Fixed 'add rule from response' not saving</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.6.2</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed matched whole value and case sensitive not being correctly pre-filled</li>
            <li>Added indication to requests/responses which have been changed by the debugger</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.6.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Headers are now displayed with the first letters capitalized</li>
            <li>Fixed issue where rule config was broken</li>
            <li>Quickly create new rule by right clicking request</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.6.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Start bringing back debugging - rewrite only</li>
            <li>Fixed stack traces sometimes disappearing</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.5.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Show warnings in connect dialog when adb paths are not set.</li>
            <li>Load adb again when it suddenly could be found by settings.</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.5.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Support dart stack traces</li>
            <li>Removed html pretty rendering with javafx, not included in JDKs anymore</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.4.2</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed issue where idevice processes would not be cleaned up in all scenarios</li>
            <li>Provided a more robust check of iproxy command status</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.4.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed issue where the manually provided adb path could cause issues listing devices</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.4.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Discover i-devices connected over usb using libimobiledevice (mac only for now)</li>
            <li>Provide settings UI to manually provide the paths for adb and libimobiledevice</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.3.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed copy-key-and-value not copying key in general panel</li>
            <li>When viewing an in-progress message, update UI when the response arrives</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.3.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>When no content type is provided, try to check if it is plain text</li>
            <li>More support for text/* mime types</li>
            <li>When the body cannot be determined, assume binary instead of empty</li>
            <li>Add save button on body panel. This saves the raw body to a file</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.2.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed issue where the UI would sometimes not fully reflect the connection status</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.2.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Network headers that differ from the application headers are now shown on the detail panel with an asterisk (*) in front of the name</li>
            <li>Updated background of stack trace panel</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.1.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Cached responses are now displayed differently</li>
            <li>Missing network requests and responses in linked view</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
        <b>2.0.0 - Complete internal rework!</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Tighter integration with intellij platform</li>
            <li>Performance optimizations</li>
            <li>Icons have been updated to better integrate into the new look</li>
            <li>SVG icons for crisp visuals!</li>
        </ul>
    </p>
        ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <idea-version since-build="181.0" />

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="plugin_withjava.xml">com.intellij.modules.java</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="plugin_withdart.xml">Dart</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="plugin_withandroid.xml">org.jetbrains.android</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="Niddler" anchor="bottom" factoryClass="com.chimerapps.niddler.ui.NiddlerToolWindowFactory" icon="/niddler_small.png" />
        <applicationConfigurable instance="com.chimerapps.niddler.ui.settings.ApplicationConfigurationProvider" id="NiddlerRoot" />
        <projectConfigurable instance="com.chimerapps.niddler.ui.settings.ProjectConfigurationProvider" parentId="NiddlerRoot" />
        <applicationService
            serviceImplementation="com.chimerapps.niddler.ui.settings.NiddlerSettings" />
        <projectService serviceImplementation="com.chimerapps.niddler.ui.settings.NiddlerProjectSettings" />

        <postStartupActivity implementation="com.chimerapps.niddler.ui.provider.ProjectStartupActivity" />

        <consoleFilterProvider implementation="com.chimerapps.niddler.ui.provider.ConnectConsoleFilterProvider" order="first" />

    </extensions>

    <actions>

    </actions>

</idea-plugin>